(Sheldon:)If a photon is directed through a plane
with two slits in it and either is observed...
(Sheldon:)...it will not go through both.
If unobserved, it will.
If it's observed after it left the plane,
before it hits its target...
(Sheldon:)- ...it will not have gone through both slits.
- Agreed.
(Leonard:)What's your point?
(Sheldon:)There's no point,
I just think it's a good idea for a T-shirt.
- Excuse me.
- Hang on.
(Leonard:)One across is Aegean,
eight down is Nabokov.
(Leonard:)Twenty-six across is MCM.
(Leonard:)Fourteen down is...
(Leonard:)Move your finger.
...phylum, which makes 14 across
Port-Au-Prince.
(Leonard:)See, Papa Doc's capital idea,
that's Port-Au-Prince.
(Leonard:)Haiti.
- Can I help you?
- Yes.
Um, is this the high-IQ sperm bank?